affiliatenichepacks.com 2010-05-13

# Disclaimers | Affiliate Niche Research Packs

**Earnings Disclaimer**

Every effort has been made to accurately represent this product and it’s potential. Even though this industry is one of the few where one can write their own check in terms of earnings, there is no guarantee that you will earn any money using the techniques and ideas in these materials. Examples in these materials are not to be interpreted as a promise or guarantee of earnings. Earning potential is entirely dependent on the person using our product, ideas and techniques. I do not purport this as a “get rich scheme.”

Any claims made of actual earnings or examples of actual results can be verified upon request. Your level of success in attaining the results claimed in my materials depends on the time you devote to the program, ideas and techniques mentioned your finances, knowledge and various skills. Since these factors differ according to individuals, I cannot guarantee your success or income level. Nor am I responsible for any of your actions.

Materials in my product and our website may contain information that includes or is based upon forward-looking statements within the meaning of the securities litigation reform act of 1995. Forward-looking statements give my expectations or forecasts of future events. You can identify these statements by the fact that they do not relate strictly to historical or current facts. They use words such as “anticipate,” “estimate,” “expect,” “project,” “intend,” “plan,” “believe,” and other words and terms of similar meaning in connection with a description of potential earnings or financial performance.

Any and all forward looking statements here or on any of my sales material are intended to express my opinion of earnings potential. Many factors will be important in determining your actual results and no guarantees are made that you will achieve results similar to mine or anybody else’s, in fact no guarantees are made that you will achieve any results from our ideas and techniques in my material.

**Disclosure**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received will not influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

I may be compensated to provide opinions on products, services, websites and various other topics mainly through affiliate commissions. Even though I receive compensation for my posts or advertisements, I always give my honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely my own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to [http://www.disclosurepolicy.org](http://www.disclosurepolicy.org/)

**Privacy Policy**

I have a firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. I hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses my information gathering and dissemination practices.

I recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and this policy is designed to assist you in understanding how I collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to me and to assist you in making informed decisions when using this site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and my customers’ needs.

What Information Do I Collect?  
When you visit this web site you may provide me with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the website.

1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration Information  
When you register for my newsletter or purchase products, you will provide us information about yourself.

Credit Card Information  
If you choose to make a purchase, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:  
-Name  
-Mailing address  
-Email address  
-Credit card number  
-Name on credit card  
-Credit card billing address  
-Business and home phone number

Shipping Information

If your product is shipped directly from the manufacturer, then I will need to provide your name and shipping address to the manufacturer. I will not share your credit card information at any time.

Email Information  
If you choose to correspond with me through email, I may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. I will not share your e-mail address with anyone.

Occasionally, I may also use the information I collect to notify you about important changes to the Website, new services, and special offers I think you will find valuable. You may notify me at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing me at the link provided on the newsletter.

2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial websites, this website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how the  website is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, and time spent at the website.

How Do I Use the Information That You Provide to Me?

Broadly speaking, I use personal information for purposes of administering  business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment,, to monitor the use of the service,  marketing and promotional efforts and improve my content and service offerings, and customize the site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve the site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personal identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

What Are Cookies?  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

How Do I Use Information I Collect from Cookies?  
As you visit and browse the Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, I also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with Web server’s log files, allow me to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps gather feedback to constantly improve the Web site and better serve my clients. Cookies do not allow me to gather any personal information about you and I do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

IP Addresses  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by the web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

Sharing and Selling Information  
I do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that I collect online and maintain in my database by completing the contact form found on the site.

What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?  
I may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when I, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of my legal rights. I may also disclose account information when I have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of my users and the Public.

What About Other Web Sites Linked to This Web Site?  
I am not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from my Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of this Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from this Website to another web site, my Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on my Website, is subject to that web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

Your Consent  
By using our Web site you consent to my collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. I reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

My Commitment To Data Security:  
Please note that your information will be stored and processed on my computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, I have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information I collect online.

Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out  
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing I will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

Surveys & Contests  
From time-to-time this site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

A Special Note About Children  
Children are not eligible to use my services unsupervised and I ask that children (under the age of 16) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

Acquisition or Changes in Ownership  
In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred. I will inform you before such a transaction takes place, giving you ample time to opt-out if you wish.

Policy Modifications  
I may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, I will email users who have given me permission to do so. I will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, I will not use the personal information you have submitted to me under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
